what is your sister's birthday okay it's
one of
two days one of the days is the 21st of
july the other day
is the 22nd until i feel even throw up
her birthday's in august taylor i'm so
sorry but
hi i'm dave mazzone and welcome to fixd
this is the show where i do a big line
of my guests insecurities
get on their level ride the high help
them come down my guest today is like so
many of us
no not doomed by global warming addicted
to their cell phones
let's get fixed hey i'm taylor ortega
i'm here today because the amount of
time i spend on my phone
i can't seem to hold a job they keep
telling me it's
time theft and i don't know what that is
and i keep thinking i'm gonna look it up
but then i'll open my phone and i'll
open instagram instead and then it's
like i always keep forgetting to look up
what time theft is
and my phone is here today because i'm
here today why wouldn't i
bring my phone
when gut renovating the soul before
installing the marble countertops 12
burner gas range and farmhouse sink
one must take a wrecking ball to
themselves
taylor i invite you here today to
renovate your heart are you ready for
that
yes amazing oh so give me your phone no
okay taylor i'm going to need you to
give me the phone okay and it's only
going to be for a little while and this
is for your betterment okay
what could possibly happen
okay so what is your password well tay
sucks
alrighty we're in and that's cheeky and
i kind of like that thank you i am going
to go through your browser tabs
so you've wikipedia just the year 1998.
yes i wanted to know what happened you
googled get down
boogie oogie yogi oh i wanted to know
what that song was claudia conway
she got her mom fired leo so sick oh
it's about to break up
noodle the best noodles you need them
pharaoh what is it alexa chong age is
she six or sixty
a day in the life of zendaya what is she
doing up there
okay great i'm gonna switch gears a
little bit i think okay now move over to
the screen time okay i'm interested to
know
taylor yeah um here call me him okay
your screen time says you haven't been
off your phone for longer than 11
minutes
i want to set an achievable goal today
something something that will make you
better yeah
so i want to take you from 11 minutes
and i'm going to bring you
to 12. the most insane thing my phone
has survived
i was in paris and i was walking down a
flight of stairs for a restaurant and i
slept which happens a lot and i went to
go grab for the railing but i
accidentally just slid my phone
down a jagged rock wall so that was
pretty bad
so taylor i want to talk to you a little
bit about your addiction
in order to separate from something you
must create a physical memory
attached to the breakup okay i will now
ask you a series of questions of things
you should know
and that any average person would know
when stripped of their phone okay okay
and for every wrong answer i will smash
your phone with this hammer
no no wait question one sutton foster's
age 45
your next question when is your parents
anniversary
taylor it happened before i was born so
give me a guess
it's in july girl what is the capital of
maine maine
main main and you think the capital of
mexico i don't think why does it sound
right
it's augusta no the emmys air on which
network it rotates yes correct that's a
trick question
what is my middle
[Music]
chris taylor we've known each other for
20 years christopher no
jameson no swayze no swayze
from mizzonio
i need a cigarette i'm sorry i can't do
this am i crying am i crying right now
this will be fine i have insurance to me
it's just like
if you can't keep your phone alive how
are you gonna be a mother someday
i'm gonna be a really good mom taylor
now that we've severed ties completely
we have the opportunity to do fun stuff
without our phone
like you know go to the park kayak pay
with cash
write a poem so you are a comedian right
yeah
tragic tell me a joke okay i actually
like wearing a face mask because i never
learned to blend my foundation onto my
neck
that's hilarious thank you i'm actually
going to tweet you really quickly
wait before we do that okay before we go
tweeting i want to introduce you to
something
it's called pen and paper and i want you
to try
writing the joke that you just said to
me out loud right here in this notebook
like this um no not like that that's not
really how you do it but it must be your
first time so
so i'm gonna take it out of this book
here and we're gonna look at it together
and then we're gonna whoo why yeah cause
you know what taylor
no one needs to see this now she's gonna
retweet this like katie l i mean
i'm probably not because she's a little
busy right now what do you mean
bye now cutie ellis guy she's bi
what but i i thought she was talking
about steve
seems gay steve is gay both gaming
i know they were engaged i know
i
and we are having fun
[Music]
okay oh thank god it was literally
foolish i wasn't gonna talk about
anything else congratulations you got to
12 minutes i
am not even lying to you i feel like a
completely different person oh my god
katie texted me it's good that you just
said it should we send her a pic
she'll kind of it'll piss her off but i
kind of like that
you